Guide to the National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
- Series X. Director of Youth Activities, Wib Justi
  - GPC - Correspondence - CARE - Grange Guatemala Project, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Circle "K" Industries, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Elyash - Grange Guatemala Project, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Fritz, Dale - Grange Guatemala Project, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Goering, Jim, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Hadlock, Ed, 1965, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Heifer Project, Inc., 1963, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    Includes Dale Barnard, Grange Guatemala Project.
  - GPC - Correspondence - Keysar, Jack, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Lane, C. R., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - GPC - Correspondence - MacArthur, 1965, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    Includes Diana T. MacArthur, Division of Private and International Organizations: Peace Corps.
  - GPC - Correspondence - Menke, D., Elizabeth, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Swanson, Bert, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Vaccaro, Frank and Edna, 1965, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    Includes Guatemala Rabbit Protein Project.
  - GPC - Correspondence - Vaughn, Jack, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Wiggins, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - GPC - Correspondence - Movies and Slides, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - GPC - Recruitment, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    Memo, note, outline.
  - GPC Relationships, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    Report, memos.
  - GPC Supplies - Application, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Proposed Peace Corps Contract Program, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 56 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, memos, notes, sample contract, budget, information, news letter.
  - Contests, 1958, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Standards, correspondence, application, clipping.
  - Contests: Conservation - Soil, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 2 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, essays, pamphlet.
  - Contests: Conservation - Soil, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 3 (a-d))
    Correspondence, certificates, award pin.
  - Contests: Conservation - Soil, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Notes.
  - Contests: Conservation, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, pamphlet, pin, lists.
  - Contests: Conservation - Soil, 1953-1954, 1953-1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, list, pin.
  - Contests: Conservation - Soil, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    List, essays, certificates, pin.
  - Youth Leadership Training Fund Correspondence, 1952, 1953, 1955, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 8 (a, b, c))
  - YLTF Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 27, Folder 9 (a-d))
  - YLTF Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 10 (a, b))
  - YLTF Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - YLTF Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 12 (a-k))
    Letters, newsclippings.
  - YLTF Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Code Reading Project, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, memos, code sheets.
  - Dynamic Granges - correspondence, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Farm/City, 1959-1964 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, pamphlet. Includes National Capital Area Farm - City Youth Cabinet.
  - Fireside Chats, 1956, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, memos, check sheet, pamphlets. Includes Grange Young Adults (Study Group.)
  - Grange Youth Achievement Key Award - 1959-1960, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 18 (a-h))
    Correspondence, entry forms.
  - Grange Youth Achievement Key Award - 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    Note, news clipping.
  - Grange Youth Achievement Key Award - 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    Notes, memo, corrected entry form.
  - National Youth Fire Safety Project, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Projects, 1954-1964 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, clippings, articles on Grange Youth Projects.
  - "A" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1964 (Box 27, Folder 23 (a, b))
    Correspondence, pamphlets, invitation.
  - Allied Chemical and Dye Corporation: Nitrogen Division, 1953-1962 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, invitations, pamphlet, bulletin.
  - Allied Youth, 1949-1963 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, article. Includes W. Roy Breg, Allied Youth, Inc.
  - Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., 1956-1963 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, invitations.
  - Alpha Gamma Rho - correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Alpha Zeta, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    Includes L. H. Dennis, Chester S. Hutchinson, College of Agriculture, Ohio State University.
  - American Automobile Association - correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - American Country Life Association, Inc. - correspondence, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - American Export Lines, 1952, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, note. Includes C. A. Deeds, N. D. Pasco, Rural Teen-ager Exchange.
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1951-1958 (Box 27, Folder 32 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, minutes. Includes Carlysle De LaCroix, Warren Newberry, Richard Nelson, Rural Youth Department, Rural Teen-ager Exchange.
  - American Field Service, 1952-1958 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    Includes George H. Edgell, Rural Teen-ager Exchange.
  - American Friends of the Middle East, 1959, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, list. Includes Barbara Shannon.
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    Correspondence, article, reprints. Includes Edwin Randall, Rural Teen-ager Exchange.
  - American Institute of Cooperation, 1953-1964 (Box 27, Folder 36 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, questionnaire, memos, programs, registration blanks, notes. Includes Walter Jacoby, Howard McClarren, Norman Frost, AIC (Cornell Session.)
  - American Vocational Association, Inc., 1954-1956 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    Correspondence, list. Includes M. D. Mobley.
  - American Youth Foundation, 1951-1960 (Box 27, Folder 38 (a, b))
    Correspondence, pamphlets. Includes Preston G. Orwig ("Wadjepi"), Camp Minewanca, American Youth Foundation.
  - Anti-Defamation, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    Correspondence, discussion guide.
  - Automotive Safety Foundation, 1950-1964 (Box 27, Folder 40 (a, b, c))
    Includes Ira B. Rogers, John L. Marks, Education and Rural Division, Automotive Safety Foundation.
  - "B" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1964 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Booster Night - 1959 - Correspondence, 1959, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Boy Scouts, 1954-1964 (Box 27, Folder 43 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, notes, memos, statement, check sheet. Includes Elmaar H. Bakken, Charles S. Griffin, Edgar W. Wolfe, Rural Service, National Council, Boy Scouts of America.
  - Buckeye workshop, 1953-1957 (Box 27, Folder 44 (a, b))
    Correspondence, program, enrollment blank. Includes Kenneth Rinehart, Agricultural Extension Service, Ohio.
  - Business Organization, Inc. - Palmer, Dick, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    Correspondence, note.
  - "C" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1964 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    Correspondence, memo, note.
  - Camp Fire Girls, Inc., 1956, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    Includes Martha F. Allen.
  - CARE, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    Correspondence, pamphlet, photographs.
  - Champion Knitwear Co., Inc., 1953-1960 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    Correspondence, catalog. Includes Chuck McDonald.
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students - correspondence, 1951, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Cooperative Recreation Service - Rohrbough, 1954-1964 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    Correspondence, evaluation sheets. Includes Lynn Rohrbough.
  - Council on Student Travel, 1961-1964 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    Correspondence, bulletins, minutes, forms. Includes John E. Bowman.
  - "D" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Dairymen's League - Corfman, Gertrude "Woodie", 1953, 1957-1964 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    Correspondence, invitations. Includes Gertrude E. Corfman, Young Cooperator Service, Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.
  - Danish Embassy, 1951, 1953, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    Correspondence, list, cartoon. Includes O. Brahe-Pederson, Agricultural Attache, Danish Embassy, Danish Farm Training Program.
  - A. H. Dondero, Incorporated, 1952-1959 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    Correspondence, samples, decalomania. Includes Colin C. Evans.
  - Dudley - Anderson - Yutzy, 1955, 1957, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    Correspondence, plan outline. Includes Don R. Callahan.
  - "E" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1949-1964 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Empire State Observatories, 1952-1958 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    Correspondence, forms. Includes William Altuchoff.
  - "F" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, flyer, pamphlet.
  - Farm Film Foundation, 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, flyer. Includes Mrs. C. Dana Bennett.
  - Farmers and Traders Life Insurance Company, 1956-1962 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, schedule. Includes Alvin E. Hanson, Leaders' Club.
  - Firestone Tire and Rubber Company, 1954, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, telegram.
  - Folk Dancer - Herman, Michael, 1952-1960 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, draft.
  - Ford Motor Company - correspondence, 1953-1962 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Foundation for American Agriculture, 1955-1964 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Includes Charles Dana Bennett, Clarence S. Woolman Memorial.
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, 1955-1958 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, flyer.
  - Fuller Regalia and Costume Co., 1957, 1959, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, forms.
  - Future Farmers of America - National Officers - 1959, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10 (a-e))
    Correspondence, articles, bulletins, news clipping, personal data. Includes W. T. Spanton, A. W. Tenney, Agricultural Education Service, Office of Education, Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, National Advisor, Future Farmers of America.
  - Future Farmers of America - National Officers - 1959, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10 (b))
  - Future Farmers of America - National Officers - 1959, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10 (c))
  - Future Farmers of America - National Officers - 1959, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10 (d))
  - Future Farmers of America - National Officers - 1959, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10 (e))
  - Future Homemakers of America, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, invitation, list.
  - "G" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1961 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, resolution. Includes Charles R. Carrol, Jr., Public Relations, The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company.
  - General Electric Company, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, note, summary.
  - General Motors Corp. - Daneke, 1953-1963 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, invitations. Includes J. F. Fitzgerald, Department of Public Relations, General Motors Corporation.
  - German Embassy Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Includes Rural Youth Exchange (Germany) Mrs. Hanna Kipe, F. S. Schlange-Schoehingen, Embassy of the Federal Republic of Germany, Washington, D. C.
  - Girl Scouts of USA, 1952-1964 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, pamphlet, publications. Includes Anne (Mrs. Thomas J.) Ford.
  - GLF - Ranney, Warren, 1950, 1956, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, program.
  - Grange Mutual Life Company, 1960, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Includes Ursel C. Narver.
  - Greater N. Y. Council [for Foreign Students] - correspondence, 1954, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Great Northern Railway Company - correspondence, 1950, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Greyhound Bus Lines, 1953-1962 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, orders, invoices, schedule. Includes J. F. Cunningham, Overseas Division, Greyhound Lines.
  - Grocery Manufacturers of America - Frank Atchley, 1955, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, memos. Includes Frank M. Atchley.
  - "H" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Home Economics Chairmen - through 1964 - correspondence, 1950-1964 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - "I" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959, 1960, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, pamphlet, itinerary.
  - Institute of International Education, 1953-1963 (Box 28, Folder 26 (a))
    Correspondence, list, memos, minutes. Includes Kenneth Holland.
  - Institute of International Education, 1953-1963 (Box 28, Folder 26 (b))
  - Institute for International Order, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Includes Ruby Yeutter, James H. Cook.
  - International Federation of Agricultural Producers, 1951-1962 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, memos, lists, draft rules. Includes Andrew Cairns.
  - International Harvester Company - correspondence, 1951-1963 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Includes John L. McCaffrey, Sponsoring Foundation, Future Farmers of America Foundation, Inc.
  - International Recreation Association - correspondence, 1955, 1956, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Includes Robert R. Gamble.
  - "J, K, L" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Jack-Bilt Corporation, 1956, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    Correspondence, advertising. Includes Frank D. Jackson.
  - Johnson & Johnson, 1957, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, entry, rules (Johnson & Johnson Scholarship Contest.)
  - Justice Department - Devaney, A. C., 1952 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, note, list. Includes Rural Teenager Project (German and Austrian) Visas, A. C. Devaney, Adjudications Division, Immigration and Naturalization Service, United States Department of Justice.
  - "M" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957, 1963, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - "N" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1964 (Box 28, Folder 36 (a))
  - "N" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1964 (Box 28, Folder 36 (b))
  - National Canners Association, 1957-1964 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    Correspondence, invitations, program. Includes National Junior Vegetable Growers Association, "The Story of John Porter" (film about a Cornell University student.)
  - National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1952, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    Correspondence, magazine. Includes Don Brown, Catholic Youth Office (Diocese of Oklahoma City and Tulsa.)
  - National College- correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    Includes Lewis B. Carpenter.
  - National Committee on Boys and Girls Club Work, Inc. - Noble, Guy, Anderson, K., 1951-1958 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    Correspondence, report, statement. Includes Kenneth H. Anderson, G. L. Noble.
  - National Committee on Children and Youth, 1961-1964 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    Correspondence, notes, guidelines, questionnaire.
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ, 1951, 1954, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    Correspondence, message.
  - National Dairy Council - correspondence, 1959, 1961-1964 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    Includes Nancy Carter.
  - National Education Association, 1957, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    Correspondence, memo, application. Includes Albert Willis, Committee on National Contests and Activities, National Education Association.
  - National Farm-City Week Committee, 1956-1963 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    Correspondence, notes. Includes Hollis M. Seavey, Special Events Committee, National Farm-City Week.
  - National Farmers Union, 1952-1962 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    Correpsondence, list. Includes Gladys Talbott Edwards.
  - National Federation of Grange Mutual Insurance Companies - correspondence, 1954, 1956, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - National Foundation, 1959-1964 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    Correspondence, booklets. Includes Basil O'Connor, Louise E. Roy.
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1955-1959 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    Correspondence, pamphlets, bulletins, news release, agenda. Includes Basil O'Connor, C. E. Turner, Frederic C. Windoes.
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, 1955, 1960-1965 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    Correspondence, invitation, memo, agenda. Includes Grant A. Shrum.
  - National 4-H Service Committee, Inc., 1959-1964 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    Correspondence, invitation. Includes Norman C. Mindrum, National Committee on Boys and Girls Club Work.
  - National Garden Institute, 1952, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    Correspondence, list.
  - National Grange Insurance Co., 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    Correspondence, itinerary, expenses, photograph, memo. Includes Kenneth P. Colby.
  - National Grange Publicity Bureau - correspondence, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - National Midcentury Committee for Children and Youth, Inc., 1952 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    Correspondence, memo, information sheet. Includes Leonard W. Mayo.
  - National Milk Producers Federation - Norton, E. M. - correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - National Officers through 1964, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 57)
    Correspondence, memo. Includes Convention Planning Session, Home Economics Program, Alta (Mrs. Donald) Peck.
  - National Plant Food Institute, 1955, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 58)
    Correspondence, memo. Includes Conservation Essay Contest, Louis H. Wilson.
  - National Safety Council, 1953-1964 (Box 28, Folder 59 (a-f))
    Correspondence, programs, summary, agenda, announcement, memos, application, inventory form, list. Includes Harold E. Heldreth, Jim Messerschmitt, Maynard Coe, E. Gene Brown, Farm Department, National Safety Council.
  - National Vocational Agricultural Teachers Association, 1957-1964 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - New Jersey, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 61)
    Correspondence, budget for New Jersey State Grange Youth Fund.
  - "O" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 28, Folder 62)
    Includes Operation Moral Upgrade.
    Correspondence, newsletter, list.
  - Ohio Council of Churches - Town and Country Department - correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Ohio Farm Bureau - correspondence, 1950, 1952, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Optimist International, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 65)
    Correspondence, information. Includes Youth Appreciation Week, Ralph J. Gentles.
  - "P" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1963 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Pan American Union, 1961, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 67)
    Correspondence, publications.
  - "R" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1962 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Reports - Lobbying, 1951, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 69)
    Receipts, report.
  - Republic Steel Corp. - Merrill, Earl D., 1953, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 70)
    Correspondence, reprint. Includes Agricultural Extension Bureau, Republic Steel Corporation.
  - Rockefeller Center - information, 1956-1959 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - Rural Teenager Project: Placement Lists 1951-1952, 1951, 1952, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 72 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, list, map.
  - Rural Teenager Project: Placement List - 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 73 (a, b))
  - "S" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - Sears-Roebuck Foundation, 1958-1963 (Box 28, Folder 75)
    Correspondence, program, note, report from the Potomac Grange Committee on Child Labor.
  - Shinner Foundation, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 76)
    Includes Farm Policy, E. G. Shinner.
  - Simplicity Pattern Co. Inc. - correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 28, Folder 77)
    Includes Nadine Thompson.
  - Singer Sewing Machine Company - correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - Square Dance Associates - Ed Durlacher, 1951-1960 (Box 28, Folder 79)
    Correspondence, itineraries.
  - Standard Oil Co., 1953, 1955, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 80)
    Notes, correspondence.
  - State Juvenile. Superintendents through 1964 - correspondence, 1953-1964 (Box 28, Folder 81 (a, b))
  - State Lecturers through 1964, 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 82)
    Correspondence, news clipping, notes. Includes Harriet E. Francisco, Marna Helen Case, New York State Grange, Arkansas State Grange.
  - State Masters through 1964 - correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 28, Folder 83 (a-i))
    Includes Leland D. Smith, New York State Grange.
  - State Grange Secretaries through 1964 - correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 28, Folder 84 (a, b, c))
  - State Youth Leader - Arkansas - correspondence, 1959-1962, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Includes Martha (Mrs. G. A.) Hendrix, Jr., Arkansas State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - California - correspondence, 1962, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - State Youth Leader - Connecticut, 1964, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, note, pamphlet. Includes Dorothy M. (Mrs. Emil) Kasperait, Connecticut State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Delaware, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, check list. Includes Lawrence Jestice, Delaware State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Florida, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, check lists. Includes Sara (Mrs. Ronald) Brockway, Florida State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Idaho, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, check list. Includes Keith Amende, Idaho State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Kansas - correspondence, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - State Youth Leader - Maine - correspondence, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Includes Richard Paul, Maine State Grange Youth Committee.
  - State Youth Leader - Massachusetts, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, check list. Includes John W. Bower, Massachusetts State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Missouri - correspondence, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Includes LeRoy and Doris Calvert, Alice (Mrs. Marion) Roebuck.
  - State Youth Leader - Montana, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Includes Pat (Mrs. Jack) Iman, Montana State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Nebraska, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, checklists. Includes Gertrude (Mrs. Walter) Bereuter, Nebraska State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - New Jersey - correspondence, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Includes Jessie (Mrs. Stuart) Hartung, New Jersey State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - North Carolina - correspondence, 1963, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Includes Brady L. Angell, North Carolina State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Oklahoma - correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Includes Adela (Mrs. Cleo) Ingle, Oklahoma State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Oregon, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, schedule. Includes Neil Cullison, Oregon State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - South Carolina - correspondence, 1961, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - State Youth Leader - South Dakota - correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Includes Georgia M. (Mrs. Jack) Cook, South Dakota State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Texas - correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Includes Maurice Theis, Texas State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Virginia, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 20 (a, b))
    Correspondence, report, photographs. Includes Doris Ann Bragg, Virginia State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Washington - correspondence, 1963, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Includes Lawrence P. Walls, Washington State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - West Virginia - correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Includes Lucille Clegg, West Virginia State Grange.
  - State Youth Leader - Wyoming - correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Includes Pearl (Mrs. Charles) Buell, Wyoming State Grange.
  - Swift & Company - correspondence, 1953-1964 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    Includes Don Moeller, Agricultural Research Department, Swift & Company.
  - "T" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, program, pamphlet. Includes Neil C. Hurley, Jr., Thor Power Tool Company, Thor Research Center for Better Farm Living.
  - Technical Assistance Information Clearing House, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, profile information, sample profile. Includes Grange Peace Corps Guatemala Project.
  - Testimony, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    Summaries, statement, release, Bill, agenda related to Federal Youth Correction Act.
  - Transport and Travel Contractors, Inc., 1954, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 28)